Register of the Wladyslaw Anders Collection, 1939-1946.
Hoover Institution Archives
- MATERIALS FILED BY DOCUMENT NUMBER
  - Doc. No. 516d - "Poczatki Niewoli Zolnierzy Polskich w ZSSR" (The Beginnings of Imprisonment of Polish Soldiers in the USSR) (Folder 23)
  - Doc. No. 517d - "Transportowanie Jencow Polskich w ZSSR w Latach 1940/1941" (The Transportation of Polish POWs to the USSR in the Years 1940/1941) (Folder 24)
  - Doc. No. 518a - "Obozy Jencow Polskich" (Polish POW Camps) (Folder 25)
  - Doc. No. 519a - "Zolnierze Polscy Internowani Na Litwe i Lotwie" (Polish Soldiers Interned in Lithuania and Latvia) (Folder 26)
  - Doc. No. 553a - "Obozy Internowanych Na Litwie i Lotwie Do Lipca-Sierpnia 1940 r." (Internment Camps in Lithuania and Latvia for the Months of July-August 1940) (Folder 27)
  - Doc. No. 555 - "Wschodnia Granica Rzeczypospolitej Polskiej" (The Eastern Border of the Republic of Poland) (Folder 28)
  - Doc. No. 556 - "Zydzi Polscy Pod Wladza Sowiecka" (The Jews of Poland under Soviet Authority) (Folder 29)
  - Doc. No. 557 - "Kogo Zwyciezono w Warszawie?" (Who Was Defeated in Warsaw?) (Folder 30)
  - Doc. No. 558 - "Problem Polski" (The Polish Problem), November 2, 1944 (Folder 31)
  - Doc. No. 559 - "Recenzje Ksiazek Pruszajacych Zagadnienia Rosyjskia" (Reviews of Books Dealing with Russian Problems), 1943-1944 (Folder 32)
  - Doc. No. 561 - "Zly Sen" (Bad Dream) (Folder 33)
  - Doc. No. 564 - "Zwiazek Patriotow Polskich" (Union of Polish Patriots) (Box 73., Folder 1)
  - Doc. No. 566 - "Zona" (The Zone), 1945 (Folder 2)
  - Doc. No. 567 - "Tomorrow We Shall Grub Again" (Folder 3)
  - Wybrane dokumenty - ich spis (documents which were pulled - a list) (Folder 4)
  - Doc. Nos. 348-371 - Stosunki Polsko-Rosyjskie (Polish-Russian relations) (Folder 5)
  - Doc. Nos. 372-390 - Stosunki Polsko-Rosyjskie (Polish-Russian relations) 1921-1939 (Folder 6)
  - Doc. Nos. 391-405 - Stosunki Polsko-Rosyjskie (Polish-Russian relations) 1939-1941 (Folder 7)
  - Doc. Nos. 406-421 - Stosunki Polsko-Rosyjskie (Polish-Russian relations) 1941-1943 (Folder 8)
  - Doc. Nos. 422-453 - Stosunki Polsko-Rosyjskie (Polish-Russian relations) 1943 (Folder 9)
  - Wykaz obozow pracy przymusowej i ich oddzialow (list of forced labor camps and their departments) (Folder 10)
  - Formularz ankiety "praca" (questionnaire blank for "work") (Folder 11)
  - List Jana Berdel z dnia 24/I/1944 (letter from Jan Berdel of January 24, 1944) (Folder 12)
  - "Eastern Poland, 1939-1941" (Folder 13)
  - Wyciagi z listow z Rosji Sowieckiej (excerpts from letters from Soviet Russia) (Folder 14)
  - Doc. No. 617 - Wykaz zamordowanych w lesie Katynskim (list of those killed in the Katyn Forest) (Folder 15)
  - Doc. No. 621 - Nota Molotowa z 12/I/1942, dot. grabiezy i zbrodni niem. (note of Molotov, January 12, 1942, regarding the looting and crimes of the Germans) (Folder 16)
  - Doc. No. 621b - Note of Molotov, January 12, 1942, regarding the looting and crimes of the Germans (Folder 17)
  - Doc. No. 622 - "Rzad Polski w Londynie i Rzad Warszawski w Swietle Prawa" (The Polish Government in London and the Warsaw Government in the Light of the Law) (Folder 18)
  - Doc. No. 624 - "Szkic o Wplywach Sowieckich w Stanach Zjednoczonych i Polonii Amerykanskiej" (Essay on Soviet Influences in the United States and American Poland), January 1945 (Folder 19)
  - Doc. No. 625b - Kodeks Karny R.S.F.S.R. (Criminal Code of the RSFSR) (Folder 20)
  - Doc. No. 626a - Akt oskarzenia abrodniarzy wojennych niemieckich odczytany w Berlinie (Indictment act of German war criminals read in Berlin), October 18, 1945 (Box 74., Folder 1)
  - Doc. No. 629 - Spis rodzin wojskowych wywiezionych do ZSSR (List of military families deported to the USSR), August 1944 (Folder 2-6)
  - Doc. No. 630a - "Kobieta Tragiczna" (The Tragic Woman) (Folder 7)
  - Doc. No. 633 - "An Outline of Polish Affairs, 1939-1945" (Folder 8)
  - Amtliches material zum Massenmord von Katyn (Official materials on the mass murder of Katyn) (Folder 9)
  - Amtliches material zum Massenmord von Katyn (Official materials on the mass murder of Katyn) (Box 75., Folder 1)
  - Release certificates from Soviet concentration camps
    - Doc. No. D88 - Rammel, Kazimierz, February 20, 1942 (Folder 2)
    - Doc. No. D128 - Sokhatskii, Vladislav, December 29, 1941 (Folder 3)
    - Doc. No. D130 - Dobek, Felix, October 11, 1941 (Folder 4)
    - Doc. No. D134 - Tadeusiak, Stanislav, August 31, 1941 (Folder 5)
    - Doc. No. D136 - Koserkevich, Iosif Antonovich, September 4, 1941 (Folder 6)
    - Doc. No. D169 - Dziubinskii, Roman Iuzefovich, September 2, 1941 (Folder 7)
    - Doc. No. D234 - Wozniak, Prantsishkus I., October 1, 1941 (Folder 8)
    - Doc. No. D254 - Sakhanovich, Mikhail Petrovich, September 22, 1941 (Folder 9)
    - Doc. No. D276 - Kozlowskii, Georgii, September 25, 1941 (Folder 10)
    - Doc. No. D278 - Reder, Michal, August 28, 1941 (Folder 11)
    - Doc. No. D279 - Shumega, Adam V, August 28, 1941 (Folder 12)
    - Doc. No. D323 - Khodorovskii, Ivan Antonovich, July 28, 1941 (Folder 13)
    - Doc. No. D362 - Zhomer, Vasilii Ermolaevich, September 16, 1941 (Folder 14)
    - Doc. No. D393 - Szopian, Tadeusz, October 1, 1942 (Folder 15)
    - Doc. No. D425 - Binek, Iozef Martinovich, January 3, 1942 (Folder 16)
    - Doc. No. D434 - Paulo, Taduesz A., October 10, 1941 (Folder 17)
    - Doc. No. D437 - Login, Wladyslaw M., December 15, 1941 (Folder 18)
    - Doc. No. D440 - Ruzycki, Adam, January 15, 1942 (Folder 19)
    - Doc. No. D477 - Sadowski, Eduard B., August 23, 1941 (Folder 20)
    - Doc. No. D489 - Vitiuk, Vasilii A., September 19, 1941 (Folder 21)
  - Doc. No. D494 - Receipt for documents, NKDV, Department of Visas and Registrations of Foreigners, Kazimierz Nowak, February 15, 1942 (Folder 22)
  - Release sertificates from Soviet Concentration Camps
    - Doc. No. D521 - Guzowski, Feliks, August 28, 1941 (Folder 23)
    - Doc. No. D525 - Falkowski, Stepan M., January 19, 1942 (Folder 24)
    - Doc. No. D597 - Ugorenko, Bronislaw S, September 17, 1941 (Folder 25)
    - Doc. No. D599 - Marshalek, Karol V, August 25, 1941 (Folder 26)
    - Doc. No. D682 - Burba, Witold B., August 28, 1941 (Folder 27)
  - Doc. No. D745 - Court sentence for Polish citizens in a Ukrainian regional court, November 1941 (Folder 28)
  - Release certificates from Soviet concentration camps
    - Doc. No. D824 - Ostrowski, Ivan I., October 25, 1941 (Folder 29)
    - Doc. No. D829 - Judzicki, Michal, October 24, 1941 (Folder 30)
    - Doc. No. D854 - Aktanarowicz, Miczieslaw, September 1, 1941 (Folder 31)
    - Doc. No. D879 - Sarna, Roman T., October 1, 1941 (Folder 32)
    - Doc. No. D883 - Sadowksi, Aleksandr, September 4, 1941 (Folder 33)
    - Doc. No. D899 - Kucharczyk, Feliks, September 3, 1941 (Folder 34)
    - Doc. No. D914 - Litskevich, Konstantin K., September 1, 1941 (Folder 35)
    - Doc. No. D919 - Nikolaiskii, Mieczeslaw, October 23, 1941 (Folder 36)
    - Doc. No. D965 - Oskerko, Evgenii, September 21, 1941 (Folder 37)
    - Doc. No. D974 - Khrushch, Zenon M., September 3, 1941 (Folder 38)
    - Doc. No. D976 - Piatek, Marian A., February 21, 1942 (Folder 39)
    - Doc. No. D1058 - Oberek, Ivan I., February 13, 1942 (Folder 40)
    - Doc. No. D1065 - Kozlowski, Anton A., September 8, 1941 (Folder 41)
    - Doc. No. D1171 - Stankiewicz, Stanislaw A., October 22, 1941 (Folder 42)
  - Doc. No. D1226 - Pismo placowki K.W. Nr. 5 z 9/VI/1943, L dz. 1051 (Letter from Office K.W. Nr. 5 of June 9, 1943, L. dz. 1051) (Folder 43)
  - Doc. No. D1226 - Odpis listu por. Piotra Dubinski, 28/IV/43 (Copy of Lieutenant Piotr Dubinski's letter, April 28, 1943) (Folder 44)
  - Doc. No. D1226 - Pismo Sekcji Bezpieczenstwa 7DP z 8/VI/1943, Nr. 923 (Letter of the Security Department 7DP of June 8, 1943, Nr. 923) (Folder 45)
  - Doc. No. D1227 - Meldunek ppor. Lapinski z 4 maja 1943 (Report of 2nd Lieutenant Lapinski, May 4, 1943) (Folder 46)
  - Doc. No. D1227 - Protokol przesluchania ppor. Lapinski (Interrogation report for 2nd Lieutenant Lapinski) (Folder 47)
  - Doc. No. D1235 - Depesza szyfrowa Nr. 2432 (Coded telegram No. 2432) (Folder 49)
  - Doc. No. D1235 - Zebranie wiadomosci o losie oficerow (Collection of news on the fate of officers) (Folder 50)
  - Doc. No. D1235 - Radiogram z 18/IV/43 (Radiogram of April 18, 1943) (Folder 51)
  - Doc. No. D1235 - Odpis listu ppor. Karola Pentz (Copy of a letter to 2nd Lieutenant Karol Pentz), Marcy 16, 1943 (Folder 52)
  - Doc. No. D1235 - Pismo Sekcji Bezp. 3 DSK z 6/IV/43 L. dz. 1073 (Letter from the Security Department 3 DSK of April 6, 1943, L. dz. 1073) (Folder 53)
  - Doc. No. D1235 - Protokol przesluchania W. Piotrowska (Interrogation report for W. Piotrowska) (Folder 54)
  - Doc. No. D1235 - Notatka z dnia 26/III/42 (Note of March 26, 1942) (Folder 55)
  - Doc. No. D1235 - Pismo Dr. Laulicht z 29/VI/43 (Letter from Dr. Laulicht of June 29, 1943) (Folder 57)
  - Doc. No. D1235 - Komunikat - tlomaczenie z niemieckiego (Communique - translation from German), July 2, 1943 (Folder 58)
  - Doc. No. D1249 - Protokol przesluchania Czeslawa Kulesza (Interrogation report for Czeslaw Kulesza) (Folder 59)
  - Doc. No. D1254 - Sprawozdanie Miedzynarodowej Komisji (Report of the International Commission) (Folder 60)
  - Doc. No. D1265 - Katynski Las Smierci (Katyn Forest of Death) (Folder 61)
  - Doc. No. D1267 - "To Co Widzialam i Przezylam w Rosji Sowieckiej w Latach 1940-42" (What I Saw and Lived Through in Soviet Russia During the Years 1940-42), by Helena Antoniewicz (Folder 62)
  - Doc. No. D1272 - "I Lived with Those Who Were Murdered..." (Folder 63)
  - Doc. No. D1272 - "Mieszkalem z Tymi Ktorzy Zostali Zamordowani w Lesie pod Katynem" (I Lived with Those Who Were Murdered in the Katyn Forest), February 6, 1944 (Folder 64)
  - Doc. No. D1273 - Wycinki prasowe z Nowy Swiat (Press clippings from Nowy Swiat), 1944 (Folder 65)
  - Doc. No. D1274 - Kommunikat Komisji Specjalnej (Communique of the Special Commission), 1944 (Folder 66)
  - Doc. No. D1275 - Signal, wydanie francuskie (Signal, French edition), No. 12, 1943 (Folder 67-68)
  - Doc. No. D1283 - "Jutro Znow Karczujemy" (Tomorrow We Will Clear the Land Again), by Jerzy Woszcynin, Iraq-Persia, 1943 (Box 75A, Folder 1)
  - Doc. No. D1285 - "Zona" (The Zone), by Jerzy Woszczynin, Persia-Iraq-Palestine (Folder 2)
  - Doc. No. D1286 - "Polozhenie o dovol'stvii Ukhto-Pechorskogo ispravitel'no-tradovogo lageria NKVD" (Instructions concerning provisions in the Ukhto-Pechora Forced Labor Camp of NKVD), May 27, 1937 (Folder 3)
  - Doc. No. D1288 - Radio exress (in Polish), April 20, 1943 (Folder 4)
  - Doc. No. D1340 - Odpis protokolu przesluchania Aleksandra Palusiak (Copy of Aleksander Palusiak's interrogation report) (Folder 5)
  - Doc. No. D1342 - Wyciag z protokolu z dnia 29/5/46 (Excerpt from the minutes of the day, May 29, 1946); skiec lasku Katynskiego (sketch of the Katyn Forest) (Folder 6)
  - Doc. No. D1348 - Pismo dra Dziadosz (Letter of Dr. Dziadosz), May 1943 (Folder 7)
  - Doc. No. D1348 - Pismo do Papieza Piusa XII, zlozone u Patriarchy Jerozolimy i Transjordanii (Letter to Pope Pius XII, deposited with the Patriarch of Jerusalem and Transjordania) (Folder 8)
  - Doc. Nos. 15723, 15725, 15739 - Odpis z odpisu (Copy from a copy) (Folder 9)
  - Doc. Nos. 15777-15778 - Odpis protokolu przesluchania (Copy of an interrogation report) (Folder 10)
  - Doc. No. 15863 - "Historia Obozu Polskich Jencow Wojennych w ZSSR - Starobielsk" (A History of the Polish Prisoners of War Camp in the USSR - Starobielsk), September 1939-May 1940 (Folder 11)
  - Zasady Budowy Katalogu Rzeczowego (The Principles of Putting Together a Subject Catalog) (Folder 12)
  - Odezwa Bevina do zolnierzy polskich (Bevin's appeal to Polish soldiers) (Folder 13)
  - Doc. No. 1077- Pamietnik H. Poszwinskiego (Memoirs of H. Poszwinski) (Folder 14)
  - Doc. No. 1186 -Akt oskarzenia (Indictment) (Folder 15)
  - Doc. No. 1193 -Wyrok (Court sentence) (Folder 16)
  - Doc. No. 1194 -Protokol rozprawy sadowej (Record of court proceedings) (Folder 17)
  - Doc. No. 1195 -Wyrok (Court sentence); protokol rozprawy sadowej (record of court proceedings) (Folder 18)
  - Doc. No. 1196 -Wyrok (Court sentence) (Folder 19)
  - Doc. No. 1187 -Protokol rozprawy sadowej i wyrok (Record of court proceedings and court sentence) (Folder 20)
  - Doc. No. 1198 -Protokol rozprawy sadowej i wyrok (Record of court proceedings and court sentence) (Folder 21)
  - Doc. No. 1199 -Prosba obywateli polskich do sadu obl. w Archangielsku (Statement of Polish citizens to the Arkhangel'sk Regional Court), May 15, 1942 (Folder 22)
  - Doc. No. 1200 -Decyzja sadu w Archangielsku (Decision of the Arkhangel'sk Court), May 26, 1942 (Folder 23)
  - Doc. No. 1201 -Protokol rozprawy sadowej i wyrok (Record of court proceedings and court sentence) (Folder 24)
  - Doc. No. 1203 -Protokol rozprawy sadowej i wyrok (Record of court proceedings and court sentence) (Folder 25)
  - Doc. No. 1204 -Protokol rozprawy sadowej i wyrok (Record of court proceedings and court sentence) (Folder 26)
  - Doc. No. 1216 -O. II 6 DP meldunek o transporcie z Magadanu (O. II 6 DP report on transportation from Magadan) (Folder 27)
  - Doc. No. 1216 -O. II 6 DP meldunek o transporcie z Kotlas (O. II 6 DP report on transportation from Kotlas) (Folder 28)
  - Doc. No. 1217 -Akt oskarzenia (Indictment), January 12, 1942 (Folder 29)
  - Doc. No. 1223 -Korespondencja w sprawie ewakuacji Zydow (Correspondence concerning the evacuation of Jews) (Folder 30)
  - Doc. No. 1225 -Protokol przesluchania (Interrogation report) (Folder 31)
  - Doc. No. 1226 -Odpis listu por. Dubinskiego Piotra (Copy of Piotr Dubinski's Letter), April 28, 1943 (Folder 32)
  - Doc. No. 1226 -Korespondencja O. II w sprawie zagranicnych oficerow (Correspondence of O. II concerning officers abroad) (Folder 33)
  - Doc. No. 1231 -Informacje o losie obyw. polskich-zeslancow (Information on the fate of Polish citizens-exiles) (Folder 34)
  - Doc. No. 1232- O ruchu Uzbecko-Kazachskim w ZSSR (On the Uzbecko-Cossack Movement in the USSR), October 10, 1943 (Folder 35)
  - Doc. No. 1233 -O stosunkach polsko-sowieckich w poczatkach 1943 (On Polish-Soviet relations in the beginning of 1943) (Box 76., Folder 1)
  - Doc. No. 1234 -O losie Zydow pod okupacja niemiecka w Polsce (On the fate of Jews under the German occupation in Poland) (Folder 2)
  - Doc. No. 1235- Materialy dotyczace oficerow zaginionych w Katyniu (Materials concerning officers lost at Katyn) (Folder 3)
  - Protokol przesluchania plut. Feliksa Blaszczak (Interrogation report of Feliks Blaszczak), April-May 1943 (Folder 4)
  - Protokol przesluchania roznych osob (Interrogation report for various individuals) (Folder 5)
  - Radiogram i protokol (Radiogram and report) (Folder 6)
  - Odpis listu Edmunda Nowakowskiego (Copy of Edmund Nowakowski's letter) Nobember 13, 1942 (Folder 7)
  - Opdis listu do ppor. Karola Pentz (Copy of a letter to Carol Pentz), March 16, 1943 (Folder 8)
  - Oswiadczenie por. Jana Majdzinski (Statement by Jan Majdzinski), January 22, 1943 (Folder 9)
  - Doc. No. 1236 - Korespondencja Dowodcy Bazy Ewakuacyjno-Materialowy w Aszchabadzie (Correspondence of the Evacuation Supply Command base in Ashkhabad), January 31, 1943 (Folder 10)
  - -Meldunek plk. dypl. Perkowicza (Report of Perkowicz) (Folder 11)
  - -Korespondencja Bazy Ewakuacyjno-Materialowy w Aszchabadzie (Correspondence of the Evacuation Supply Base in Ashkhabad) (Folder 12)
  - -Sprawozdanie Dowodcy Bazy Ewakuacyjno-Materialowy w Aszchabadzie (Report of the Evacuation Supply Command Base in Ashkhabad), July 23, 1943 (Folder 13)
  - -Plk. Perkowicz do gen. Andersa, list z 30/7/1943 (Colonel Perkowicz's letter to General Anders, July 30, 1943) (Folder 14)
  - -"Przeglad Dzialolnosci na Terenie ZSSR," napisany przez Plk. Perkowicza (Survey of Activities in the USSR by Colonel Perkowicz) (Folder 15)
  - Doc. No. 1254 - Sprawozdanie Miedzynarodowej Komisji w Katyniu (Report of the International Commission in Katyn) (Folder 16)
  - Doc. No. 1256 - Notatka w sprawie Katynia (Note concerning Katyn) (Folder 17)
  - Doc. No. 1258 - Wladyslaw Suminski i tow. do Ambasady RP w Kujbyszewie (Wladslaw Suminski and company to the Polish Embassy in Kuibyshev, letter), March 29 (Folder 18)
  - Doc. No. 1259 - Wykaz "osobych Stroibatalionow" (List of "special building battalions), December 22, 1941 (Folder 19)
  - -Stroj-bataliony (Building battalions) (Folder 20)
  - Doc. No. 1260 - Zestawienie wiadomosci o zaginionych jencach wojennych (Compilation of news about missing military prisoners of war) (Folder 21)
  - Doc. No. 1261 - Rotmistr Michal Zaleski - zeznanie o Kolymie (Captain Michal Zaleski - testimony on Kolyma), November 2, 1941 (Folder 22)
  - Doc. No. 1262 - Gaszciecka - zeznanie o zatopieniu barek na Morzu Bialym (K. Gaszciecka - testimony on the sinking of barges in the White Sea), January 26, 1943 (Folder 23)
  - Doc. No. 1273 - "Kto Zamordowal 10,000 Oficerow?" (Who Murdered 10,000 Officers?) (Folder 24)
  - Doc. No. 1288 - Radio express, April 20, 1943 (Folder 25)
  - Doc. No. 1331 - Odpis listu (Copy of a letter), October 15, 1945 (Folder 26)
  - Doc. No. 1340 - Protokol Przesluchania Aleksandra Palusiak w sprawie Katynia (Interrogation report of Aleksander Palusiak concerning Katyn), May 24, 1946 (Folder 27)
  - Doc. No. 1349 - Wyjatki z listow min. Zaleskiego do gen. Sikorskiego (Excerpts from the letters of Minister Zaleski to General Sikorski), August 1941 (Folder 28)
  - Protokol tajny do ukladu, dopiero w dniu 5 kwietnia 1945 r. (Secret protocol to the agreement, made public 4/5/45) (Folder 29)
  - Nota Sowiecka z 17/1/1942 (Soviet note, 17/1/9142) (Folder 30)
  - Wykazy osob wojskowych 6 DP posiadajacych rodziny wglednie krewnych na terenie ZSSR (Lists of military personnel of the 6 DP who have family or relatives in the USSR) (Folder 31)
  - Sprawozdanie z prac od 15/5/1943 (Report from the work of 15/5/1943) (Folder 32)
  - 030843 Notatka sluzbowa (Official note) (Folder 33)
  - 090943 Notatka Sluzbowa (Official note) (Folder 34)
  - 301043 Notatka (Note) (Folder 35)
  - 051143 Notatka (Note) (Folder 36)
  - 061243 Notatka (Note) (Folder 37)
  - 141243 Szkic organizacyjny (Organizational sketch), December 14, 1943 (Folder 38)
  - 100643 Notatka (Note) (Folder 39)
  - Notatka sluzbowa (Official note) (Folder 40)
  - 080543 Notatka sluzbowa (Official note) (Folder 41)
  - 153/BD/46 Instrukcja (Instructions), January 30, 1946 (Folder 42)
  - 153/BD/46 Instrukcja (Instructions), February 14, 1946 (Folder 43)
  - 81/tj/BS/46 Oddzial Kultury i Prasy (Department of Culture and Press), February 8, 1945 (Folder 44)
  - Ankieta "Zloto" ("Gold" questionnaire) (Folder 45)
  - Formularz "Dane o czlonkach rodziny" ("Data on family members" form) (Folder 46)
  - Polski Osrodek Wojskowy (Polish Military Center), Murnau 0645 June 1945 (Folder 47)
    - Material przygotowawczy (Preparatory material) (Folder 48)
    - 150645 Apel do harcerzy (Appeal to the cavalry), June 1945 (Folder 49)
  - 130645/132/BD/tj/45 Instrukcja ankietow (Questionnaire instructions), June 1945 (Folder 50)
  - Ankieta "Zolnierzu!" ("Soldiers" questionnaire) (Folder 51)
  - Ankieta S (S Questionnaire) (Folder 52)
  - Ankieta NS (NS Questionnaire) (Folder 53)
  - 070444 Kwestionariusz (Questionnaire), April 7, 1944 (Folder 54)
  - Ankieta "Zydowska" ("Jewish" questionnaire) (Folder 55)
  - Ankieta "Praca Zbiorowa" ("Collective work" questionnaire) (Folder 56)
  - Ankieta w sprawie pracy (Questionnaire concerning work) (Folder 57)
  - Ankieta "kobieca" ("Female" questionnaire) (Folder 58)
  - Kwestionariusz gospodarczy (Economic questionnaire) (Folder 59)
  - Notatka w sprawie zbierania i opracowywania materialow informacyjnych o Rosji Sowieckiej (Note concerning the collecting and organizing of informational materials on Soviet Russia) (Folder 60)
  - Instrukcja dla opracowania materialu ankietowego (Instructions for organizing questionnaire materials) (Folder 61)
  - Instrukcja dla opracowania material ankietowy (Instructions for those organizing the questionnaire materials) (Folder 62)
  - Instrukcja dla opracowania katalogu rzeczowego (Instructions for organizing a subject catalog) (Folder 63)
  - Instrukcja dla osob sporzadzajacych kartoteke (Instructions for people preparing the card catalog) (Folder 64)
  - Wykaz akt specjalnych "A" za lata 1943-46 (List of special "A" documents for the years 1943-1946) (Folder 65)
  - Dezyderaty Rzadu w zakresie przygotowawczych prac kongresowych (Demands of the government in the area of preparing for the peace conference) (Folder 66)
  - 010343 Instrukcja (Instructions), March 1, 1943 (Folder 67)
  - 040343 Dowodztwo Armii Polskiej na Wschodzie (Polish Army in the East Headquarters), March 1943 (Folder 68)
  - 080343 Dowodztwo Rejonu Etapow Iran (Halting-place Area Headquarters in Iran), March 8, 1943 (Folder 69)
  - 2167 Radiogram z Londynu (Radiogram from London), April 10, 1943 (Folder 70)
  - 7/BD/tj/43 Biuro Dokumentow (Documents Bureau) (Folder 71)
  - 546/0.II/tj/43 - 6 DP, March 2, 1943 (Folder 72)
  - P. 2290 Radiogram z Londynu (Radiogram from London), April 1, 1943 (Folder 73)
  - 150443 Protokol o wspolpracy APW z Centrum Informacji (Document on cooperation of the Polish Army in the East with the Information Center), April 15 1943 (Folder 74)
  - 1219/I/tj/43 Dowodztwo APW (Polish Army in the East Headquarters), April 15, 1943 (Folder 75)
  - 678/Inf/43 Placowka KW nr. 5 (Outpost KW nr. 5), March 10, 1943 (Folder 76)
  - 200443 Radio express, April 20, 1943 (Folder 77)
  - 020543 Notatka sluzbowa (Official note), Telmany, May 2, 1943 (Folder 78)
  - 120443 Notatka sluzbowa (Official note), Telemany April 12, 1943 (Folder 79)
  - 21/tj/43 Ryzinski, Pplk, April 12, 1943 (Box 77., Folder 1)
  - L.2804 Radiogram z Londynu (Radiogram from London), May 2, 1943 (Folder 2)
  - 22/BD/tj/43 Radio express, May 2, 1943 (Folder 3)
  - L.832 Jerozolima (Jerusalem) radiogram, May 2, 1943 (Folder 4)
  - Centrum Informacji (Information Center), April 28, 1943 (Folder 5)
  - 120543 Dowodztwo Armii Polskiej na Wschodzie (Polish Army in the East Headquarters), May 12, 1943 (Folder 6)
  - 33/tj/43 Biuro Dokumentow (Documents Bureau), May 24, 1943 (Folder 7)
  - L.13 Rehovoth - radiogram, May 29, 1943 (Folder 8)
  - 51/tj/Kanc/43 Dowodztwo Armii Polskiej na Wschodzie (Polish Army in the East Headquarters), June 27, 1943 (Folder 9)
  - 44,48-49/tj/43 Biuro Dokumentow (Documents Bureau), April-June 1943 (Folder 10)
  - Ewidencja rodzin wojskowych pozostalych w ZSSR (Information on families of military personnel remaining in the USSR) (Folder 11)
  - 130743 Dowodca Armii Polskiej na Wschodzie (Commander-in-Chief of the Polish Army in the East), July 13, 1943 (Folder 12)
  - Notatka luzna "w zwiazku z zamierzeniem..." (Separate note "in connection with the intenton...") (Folder 13)
  - 54/tj/BD/43 Plik akt, wg spisu na odwolucie wszystkie jednostronicowe (A group of documents according to the listing on the cover, all are 1 page documents) (Folder 14)
  - 62/tj/43 Biuro Dokumentow (Documents Bureau), September 7, 1943 (Folder 15)
  - 66/tj/43 Biuro Dokumentow (Documents Bureau), March 8, 1943 (Folder 16)
  - 1469/0.II - Ochr./tj/43 Dowodztwo Bazy i Etapow Armii Polskiej na Wschodzie (Polish Army in the East Headquarters of the Base and Halting-places), September 18, 1943 (Folder 17)
  - Uwagi do istrukcji bezpieczenstwa (Notes on security instructions), August 13, 1943 (Folder 18)
  - Podpisy pracownikow Biura Dok. (Signatures of employees at the Documents Bureau), September 18, 1943 (Folder 19)
  - 89a/tj/43 Biuro Dok. (Documents Bureau), October 20, 1943 (Folder 20)
  - 12723 Dowodztwo APW (Polish Army in the East Headquarters), November 4, 1943 (Folder 21)
  - 110/tj/43 Biuro Dok. (Documents Bureau), November 13, 1943 (Folder 22)